Guide to the Myrtle Family Accounts, 1881-1920
Myrtle Family Accounts, 1881-1920
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Myrtle family accounts, 1881-1920
1172
Myrtle family.
32 v.
Farm account volumes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Farm account volumes from a farm owned by Henry C. Myrtle and later by his son Clarence Myrtle.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Farm account volumes from a farm owned by Henry C. Myrtle and later by his son Clarence Myrtle.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Myrtle family.; Myrtle, Henry C.; Myrtle, Clarence.
Subjects:
Agriculture--Accounting.; Farms--New York (State)--Bath.
Form and Genre Terms:
Account books.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Ledger, Mar. 3, 1881-Dec. 20, 1881
- Day book, 1881-1894
- Account book, Dec. 28, 1883-Dec. 18, 1885
- Accounts, Nov. 23, 1885-Dec. 10, 1888
- Accounts, Nov. 23, 1885-Dec. 31, 1889
- Accounts, June 22, 1889-Dec. 24, 1897
- Accounts, 1891-1894
- Cash accounts, Jan. 1, 1897-Jan. 11, 1901
- Day book, Jan. 2, 1899-Dec. 28, 1900
- Ledger, Jan. 2, 1899-Dec. 31, 1900
- Journal, Jan. 1, 1901-Sept. 29, 1902
- Ledger, Jan. 25, 1901-June 28, 1902
- Accounts, agricultural, 1903
- Cash accounts, Jan. 1, 1903-Sept. 29, 1906
- Cash, Dec. 31, 1904-Dec. 28, 1905
- Day book, 1906-1907
- Journal, Jan. 1, 1907-June 30, 1909
- Accounts, 1907-1909
- Day book, July 1, 1909-Jan. 19, 1910
- Cash, Mar. 29, 1909-Feb. 16, 1912
- Day book, Jan. 1, 1910-Dec. 30, 1911
- Ledger, 1910-1911
- Account, May 29, 1911-Nov. 14, 1914
- Day book, Jan. 1, 1912-Dec. 31, 1913
- Cash, Jan. 2, 1912-Jan. 23, 1915
- Expense account, Jan. 2, 1912-Oct. 31, 1918
- Cash book, Jan. 2, 1912-Jan. 9, 1919
- Journal, Jan. 1, 1914-Mar. 31, 1916
- Account, 1915-1919
- Account book, Apr. 1, 1916-Jan. 2, 1919
- Accounts, Jan. 2, 1919-Feb. 29, 1920
- Accounts, Jan. 2, 1919-Nov. 1920